Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- De Hauke & Co., Inc., Records, 1925-1949, undated, Series 9:; (Boxes 382-416; 16 linear feet)
  - Correspondence, 1925-1949, undated, 9.1:
    - Domestic Correspondence, 1926-1931, undated, 9.1.2:
      - Central Bureau for Registered Addresses, 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 3)
      - Chadbourne, Emily Crane, 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 4)
      - Chandler, Mrs. Porter R., 1928-1930 (Box 384, Folder 5)
      - Chase, Fielding (Mrs. J. B.), 1927-1928, undated (Box 384, Folder 6)
      - Cheney, Ward, 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 7)
      - Clark, Mrs. D. Crawford, 1927 (Box 384, Folder 8)
      - Clark, Stephen C., 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 9)
      - Clarke, Pierce, 1927-1928 (Box 384, Folder 10)
      - Coburn, Mrs. Lewis L., 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 11)
      - Cochran, Gifford, 1928-1929 (Box 384, Folder 12)
      - Codyre, Patrick, 1930 (Box 384, Folder 13)
      - Coe, Ralph M., 1926-1929 (Box 384, Folder 14)
      - Compagnie Générale Transatlantique ("The French Line"), 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 15)
      - Consulat Général de France, 1926-1927 (Box 384, Folder 16)
      - Crane, Josephine B. (Mrs. W. Murray), 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 17)
      - Cross, John, 1926-1927 (Box 384, Folder 18)
      - Crowinshield, Frank, 1926-1930 (Box 384, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous C, 1926-1930, undated (Box 384, Folder 20)
      - Dalton, Henry G., 1928-1929 (Box 384, Folder 21)
      - d'Ary, Jean, 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 22)
      - Davis, Howland, 1927 (Box 384, Folder 23)
      - Deeter, Paxton, 1930 (Box 384, Folder 24)
      - Delano, William A., 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 25)
      - de Monvel, Bernard Boutet, 1926-1927 (Box 384, Folder 26)
      - Demotte, Inc., 1929-1930 (Box 384, Folder 27)
      - de Vaulchier, Simon, 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 28)
      - Dewitt Clinton High School, 1929-1930 (Box 384, Folder 29)
      - Display Stage Lighting Co., 1927 (Box 384, Folder 30)
      - Downtown Gallery, 1927-1930 (Box 384, Folder 31)
      - Dows, Olin, 1927-1929 (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Draper, Muriel, 1929-1930 (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Dunbar, Mrs. John, 1927-1929 (Box 385, Folder 3)
      - Durand-Ruel, Inc., 1929-1930 (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous D, 1926-1930, undated (Box 385, Folder 5)
      - Eccles, Dr. George W., 1928-1930 (Box 385, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous E, 1926-1930, undated (Box 385, Folder 7)
      - Fisher, Elizabeth, 1928 (Box 385, Folder 8)
      - Franchi Printing Co., 1927-1928 (Box 385, Folder 9)
      - Frankl Galleries, 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 10)
      - Fraser, Charles L., 1927 (Box 385, Folder 11)
      - Frederick, Leopold, 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 12)
      - Frick Art Reference Library, 1927-1930 (Box 385, Folder 13)
      - Fry, John Hemming, 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous F, 1926-1930, undated (Box 385, Folder 15)
      - Gage Gallery, 1927-1929 (Box 385, Folder 16)
      - Gage, George E. (see Gage Gallery) (Box 385)
      - Galerie Beaux-Arts, 1930 (Box 385, Folder 17)
      - Gallatin, Albert E., 1927-1930 (Box 385, Folder 18)
      - Genthe, Dr. Arnold, 1926-1929 (Box 385, Folder 19)
      - Ginn, Mr. and Mrs. Frank H., 1926-1929 (Box 385, Folder 20)
      - Goldsmith, Morton, 1929-1930 (Box 385, Folder 21)
      - Goodwin, Phillip L., 1926-1930 (Box 385, Folder 22)
      - Goodyear, A. Conger, 1926-1930 (Box 385, Folder 23)
      - Gotham Glass Co., 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 24)
      - Gray, Mr. and Mrs. Henry, 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 25)
      - Greening, W. S., 1927-1929 (Box 385, Folder 26)
      - Guetta, René, 1926-1927 (Box 385, Folder 27)
      - Guggenheim, S. R., 1930 (Box 385, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous G, 1926-1941 (Box 385, Folder 29)
      - Hale Desk Co., 1926-1929 (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Hamershlag, Mr. and Mrs. Robert J., 1930 (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Hare & Coolidge, 1927-1928, undated (Box 386, Folder 3)
      - Harriman, Marie (Mrs. William Averell), 1926-1930 (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Harrison, William Preston, 1927-1930 (Box 386, Folder 5)
      - Haupt, Erik G., 1926-1930 (Box 386, Folder 6)
      - Havermeyer, Mrs. Horace O., 1927-1928 (Box 386, Folder 7)
      - Haven, Mrs. J. W., 1927-1929 (Box 386, Folder 8)
      - Henry Gallery, University of Washington, 1927-1928 (Box 386, Folder 9)
      - Henry Reinhardt & Son (Reinhardt Galleries), 1928-1930 (Box 386, Folder 10)
      - Hirsch, Mr. and Mrs. J. W., 1930 (Box 386, Folder 11)
      - Hirschland, Dr. F. H., 1927-1929 (Box 386, Folder 12)
      - Hochschild, Mrs. Walther, 1929-1930 (Box 386, Folder 13)
      - Hodges, Mrs. Glenn, 1926-1928 (Box 386, Folder 14)
      - Hofer, Mrs. Charles F., 1926-1927 (Box 386, Folder 15)
      - Hofer, Philip, 1927-1930 (Box 386, Folder 16)
      - Holabird, John A., 1928-1929 (Box 386, Folder 17)
      - Holl, George E., 1926-1927 (Box 386, Folder 18)
      - Holmes Protective Co., 1926-1930, undated, (not scanned) (Box 386, Folder 19)
      - Holston, William H., 1928-1930 (Box 386, Folder 20)
      - Hooven Letters, 1928-1930, undated (Box 386, Folder 21)
      - Horter, Earl, 1927-1930 (Box 386, Folder 22)
      - Hoyt, Charles B., 1928-1930 (Box 386, Folder 23)
      - Hudson, Elizabeth, 1927-1928 (Box 386, Folder 24)
      - Huntington, Margaret W., 1928, undated (Box 386, Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous H, 1926-1930, undated (Box 386, Folder 26)
      - Ingersoll, R. Sturgis, 1929-1930 (Box 386, Folder 27)
      - Insurance Company of North America, 1940 (Box 386, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous I, 1926-1929 (Box 386, Folder 29)
      - J. G. Valiant Co., 1927-1928 (Box 386, Folder 30)
      - J. Merritt Malloney's Gallery, 1928-1929 (Box 386, Folder 31)
      - Jennings, Oliver B., 1930 (Box 386, Folder 32)
      - Jewett, Rutger Bleeker, 1927-1928 (Box 386, Folder 33)
      - Johnson, Chester H., 1926-1928 (Box 386, Folder 34)
      - Jordan Marsh Co., 1928, undated (Box 386, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous J, 1926-1930 (Box 386, Folder 36)
      - Kaufmann, Edgar J., 1928-1929 (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Kerrigan, Mrs. J. J., 1928-1930 (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - King, Ethel (see Russell, Mrs. Charles H., Jr.) (Box 387)
      - King, Mrs. Frederic Rhinelander, 1928-1929 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Knight Electric Co., 1928 (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - Kraushaar, C. W., 1928-1929 (Box 387, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous K, 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 6)
      - L. Alavoine & Co., 1928-1930 (Box 387, Folder 7)
      - Labaudt, Lucien, 1930 (Box 387, Folder 8)
      - Lamb, Cathbert (Mrs. William F.), 1927-1929 (Box 387, Folder 9)
      - Lamb, Paul, 1929-1930 (Box 387, Folder 10)
      - Lane, James, 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 11)
      - Lee, Mrs. Charles T., 1929 (Box 387, Folder 12)
      - Levy, Edgar A., 1927 (Box 387, Folder 13)
      - Levy, Harriet L., 1927-1930 (Box 387, Folder 14)
      - Lewisohn, Adolph and Samuel A., 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 15)
      - Lichtenstein, Mrs. Harry, 1928-1930 (Box 387, Folder 16)
      - Liebman, Mrs. Charles J., 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 17)
      - Lord & Taylor, 1926 (Box 387, Folder 18)
      - Lorillard, Pierre, 1928-1930 (Box 387, Folder 19)
      - Lovet-Lorski, Boris, 1927, undated (Box 387, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous L, 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 21)
      - M. Knoedler & Co., Inc., 1928-1930 (Box 387, Folder 22)
      - Martin, Mrs. George A., 1929-1930 (Box 387, Folder 23)
      - Mason, Stevens T., 1928 (Box 387, Folder 24)
      - McCall, Ted C., 1926-1927 (Box 387, Folder 25)
      - McClees Galleries, 1930 (Box 387, Folder 26)
      - McKean, Mrs. Q. A. Shaw, 1929-1930, undated (Box 387, Folder 27)
      - McKnight, Mrs. William F., 1928-1929 (Box 387, Folder 28)
      - Meindl, Konrad, 1927-1928 (Box 387, Folder 29)
      - Metcalf, Thomas, 1926-1930 (Box 387, Folder 30)
      - Millet, Mrs. Stephen, 1926-1929 (Box 387, Folder 31)
      - Moffet, Douglas, 1927-1929 (Box 387, Folder 32)
      - Monvel, Bernard Boutet de (see de Monvel, Bernard Boutet) (Box 387)
      - Morton, Joseph S., 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - Muller, Burton, 1928-1930 (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - Murphy, Mrs. J. B., 1928-1929 (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous M, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 4)
      - Netcher, Mr. and Mrs. Charles N., 1927-1930 (Box 388, Folder 5)
      - New York Public Library, 1928-1930 (Box 388, Folder 6)
      - New York Telephone Company, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 7)
      - New York University, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous N, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 9)
      - Oakland Art Gallery, 1930 (Box 388, Folder 10)
      - O'Brien, Mrs. Edmond, 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 11)
      - Osborne, Sidney, 1928-1930 (Box 388, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous O, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 13)
      - P. E. Guerin, 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 14)
      - Pach, Walter, 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 15)
      - Paine, Robert Treat, II, 1927-1930 (Box 388, Folder 16)
      - Parker, Mrs. Inez E., 1928-1930 (Box 388, Folder 17)
      - Parsons, Mary, 1929-1930 (Box 388, Folder 18)
      - Pascin, Jules, 1927-1928 (Box 388, Folder 19)
      - Pepper, Charles H., 1930, undated (Box 388, Folder 20)
      - Pepper, Stephen C., 1929-1930 (Box 388, Folder 21)
      - Phillips, Duncan and Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 22)
      - Phillips, Duncan and Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1928-1930 (Box 388, Folder 23)
      - Pollack, Mrs. Fan, 1926-1927 (Box 388, Folder 24)
      - Porter, Mr. and Mrs. George F., 1926 (Box 388, Folder 25)
      - Print Club of Philadelphia, 1930 (Box 388, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous P, 1926-1930 (Box 388, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous Q, 1930 (Box 388, Folder 28)
      - R. H. Macy & Co., 1927 (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Redmond, Mrs. H. S., 1927-1928 (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Redmond, Mr. and Mrs. J. L., 1926-1929 (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - Reinhardt Galleries (see Henry Reinhardt & Son) (Box 389)
      - Remington Rand International, 1926-1930, (not scanned) (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - Richards, Charles R., 1926-1927 (Box 389, Folder 5)
      - Robineau, Adelaide A., 1926-1927 (Box 389, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., Jr., 1929-1930 (Box 389, Folder 7)
      - Rose, Mrs. A. L., 1928-1929 (Box 389, Folder 8)
      - Rose & Paskus, 1926-1930 (Box 389, Folder 9)
      - Rothbart, Albert, 1926-1930 (Box 389, Folder 10)
      - Russell, Mrs. Charles H., Jr. (née Ethel King), 1927-1930 (Box 389, Folder 11)
      - Ryerson, Martin A., 1927-1929 (Box 389, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous R, 1926-1928, undated (Box 389, Folder 13)
      - Sachs, Mrs. Arthur, 1926-1929 (Box 389, Folder 14)
      - Sachs, Howard, 1927-1930 (Box 389, Folder 15)
      - Sachs, Maurice, 1929-1930 (Box 389, Folder 16)
      - Sachs, Mr. and Mrs. Walter E., 1926-1929 (Box 389, Folder 17)
      - Saklatwalla, B. D., 1928-1930 (Box 389, Folder 18)
      - Saks & Co., 1926-1929 (Box 389, Folder 19)
      - Salinger, Jehanne Biétry, 1929-1930 (Box 389, Folder 20)
      - Satyr Book Shop, 1926-1927 (Box 389, Folder 21)
      - Scheyer, Galka E. (see Oakland Art Gallery) (Box 389)
      - Schwartz, Morton L., 1928-1929 (Box 389, Folder 22)
      - Schwarzenbach, Mrs. Robert, 1929 (Box 389, Folder 23)
      - Scott, Stevenson, 1927 (Box 389, Folder 24)
      - Seeley, Mrs. S. Ward, 1927-1928 (Box 389, Folder 25)
      - Seligmann, René, 1928-1930 (Box 389, Folder 26)
      - Seydel, L. Victor, 1927 (Box 389, Folder 27)
      - Sheridan, J. M., 1930 (Box 389, Folder 28)
      - Signer, Marjorie, 1928-1929 (Box 389, Folder 29)
      - Sinsheimer, Alexander L., 1927-1930 (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - Slade, George T., 1926 (Box 390, Folder 2)
      - Spaulding, John T., 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 3)
      - Speiser & Speiser, 1927-1930 (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - Springer, Nelson Junius, 1927-1928 (Box 390, Folder 5)
      - Springfield Printing and Binding Co., 1930 (Box 390, Folder 6)
      - Stein, Charles F., Jr., 1929 (Box 390, Folder 7)
      - Stern, Mrs. Benjamin, 1927-1931, undated (Box 390, Folder 8)
      - Stillman, C. C., 1926 (Box 390, Folder 9)
      - Stone, Maurice L., 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 10)
      - Sturges, Dorothy, 1927-1930 (Box 390, Folder 11)
      - Stursberg, Mrs. William, 1926 (Box 390, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous S, Sa-Sp, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous S, St, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 14)
      - Telling, Elisabeth, 1928-1929, undated (Box 390, Folder 15)
      - Town Hall Club, 1930 (Box 390, Folder 16)
      - Trimble, J. H., 1927 (Box 390, Folder 17)
      - Turner, Francis M., Jr., 1928 (Box 390, Folder 18)
      - Tyson, Carroll S., Jr., 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous T, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous U, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 21)
      - Valentine Gallery, 1927-1929 (Box 390, Folder 22)
      - Van Beuren, M. M., 1927 (Box 390, Folder 23)
      - Van Gerbig, Mrs. Earend, 1926-1927 (Box 390, Folder 24)
      - Vaulchier, Simon de (see de Vaulchier, Simon) (Box 390)
      - Miscellaneous V, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 25)
      - Warren, Mrs. James C., 1928-1929 (Box 390, Folder 26)
      - Watson, Mr. and Mrs. James Sibley, 1926-1929 (Box 390, Folder 27)
      - Weeks, Carl, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 28)
      - Weil, Milton, 1930 (Box 390, Folder 29)
      - Weir, Dorothy, 1926-1927 (Box 390, Folder 30)
      - Wetmore, Edith, 1926-1930 (Box 390, Folder 31)
      - Weyhe, E., 1927-1930 (Box 391, Folder 1)
      - White, Lawrence Grant, 1927-1930 (Box 391, Folder 2)
      - White, Mr. and Mrs. Samuel S., III, 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 3)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt, 1927-1930 (Box 391, Folder 4)
      - Wildenstein & Co., 1927-1929 (Box 391, Folder 5)
      - William Macbeth, Inc., 1928-1929 (Box 391, Folder 6)
      - Williams, Lewis B., 1927-1929 (Box 391, Folder 7)
      - Winston, Norman K., 1927-1929 (Box 391, Folder 8)
      - Winthrop, Grenville L., 1927-1930 (Box 391, Folder 9)
      - Wolf, Hamilton A., 1927-1930 (Box 391, Folder 10)
      - Wolfe, W. Béran, 1928-1929, undated (Box 391, Folder 11)
      - Woollcott, Alexander, 1929 (Box 391, Folder 12)
      - Worcester, Charles H., 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 13)
      - Wright, Thomas B., 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous W, 1926-1930 (Box 391, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Y, 1928-1929, undated (Box 391, Folder 16)
      - Zabel, Morton Dauwen, 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1925-1940, undated, 9.1.3:
      This subseries section includes handwritten and typewritten letters, with occasional attachments and cablegrams, with European clients about works of art, exhibitions, and related art matters.
      The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of client, and is generally in reverse chronological order within folders. This series has been scanned in entirety.
      - Anet, Claude, 1926-1930 (Box 391, Folder 18)
      - Aron, Jean, 1926-1929, undated (Box 391, Folder 19)
      - Art et Décoration (see Editions Albert Lévy) (Box 391)
      - Arthur Tooth & Sons, Ltd., 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 20)
      - Arts et Métiers Graphiques, 1929-1930 (Box 391, Folder 21)
      - Asselin, Maurice, 1926-1928 (Box 391, Folder 22)
      - Association Française d'Expansion et d'Exchanges Artistiques, 1925-1930 (Box 391, Folder 23)
      - Avila, 1926-1930 (Box 391, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous A, 1926-1930, undated (Box 391, Folder 25)
      - Barbizon House, 1928 (Box 391, Folder 26)
      - Bassiano, Princesse, 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 27)
      - Baudoin, Henri, 1929-1930 (Box 391, Folder 28)
      - Beauregard, Comte Max de, 1926-1927, undated (Box 391, Folder 29)
      - Beauvais, 1929 (Box 391, Folder 30)
      - Bellier, Alphonse, 1926-1930 (Box 391, Folder 31)
      - Bénard, Georges, 1928-1930 (Box 391, Folder 32)
      - Bernard, Joseph, 1926-1928 (Box 391, Folder 33)
      - Bernheim, Georges, 1927-1930 (Box 392, Folder 1)
      - Besson, Georges, 1930 (Box 392, Folder 2)
      - Bignou, Etienne, 1927-1930 (Box 392, Folder 3)
      - Bilis, Marc, 1929 (Box 392, Folder 4)
      - Bing & Grondahls, 1926-1927 (Box 392, Folder 5)
      - Blot, Jacques, 1928-1930 (Box 392, Folder 6)
      - Blumenthal, Florence (Mrs. George), 1926 (Box 392, Folder 7)
      - Bonfils, Robert, 1927 (Box 392, Folder 8)
      - Bonger, André, 1928-1930 (Box 392, Folder 9)
      - Bonnard, Pierre, 1926-1930 (Box 392, Folder 10)
      - Botte, Paul, 1930 (Box 392, Folder 11)
      - Bouche, Georges, 1926-1927 (Box 392, Folder 12)
      - Brame, Hector and Paul, 1929-1930 (Box 392, Folder 13)
      - Brandt, Edgar (see Maison Brandt) (Box 392)
      - Brooks, Alder, 1929-1930 (Box 392, Folder 14)
      - Bureau International des Arts Français 1928-1929 (Box 392, Folder 15)
      - Burie, André, 1926-1927 (Box 392, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous B, 1926-1940 (Box 392, Folder 17)
      - Les Cadres, 1930 (Box 392, Folder 18)
      - Carlu, Jean, 1930 (Box 392, Folder 19)
      - Cartier, Inc., 1928 (Box 392, Folder 20)
      - Casalis, Dr. H. A., 1928 (Box 392, Folder 21)
      - Cassirer, Paul, 1929-1930 (Box 392, Folder 22)
      - Cayeux, Robert, 1927-1930 (Box 392, Folder 23)
      - Ceria, Edmond, 1927-1928 (Box 392, Folder 24)
      - Cézanne, Mme. Paul, 1930 (Box 392, Folder 25)
      - Chadourne, Paul, 1928-1930 (Box 392, Folder 26)
      - Chapius, Charles and Marcel Coince, 1929-1930 (Box 392, Folder 27)
      - Chassé, Charles, 1929 (Box 392, Folder 28)
      - Chouanard, Emile, 1926 (Box 392, Folder 29)
      - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1927-1929 (Box 392, Folder 30)
      - Churchill, Lord Ivor Spencer, 1929-1930 (Box 392, Folder 31)
      - Cléret, A., 1928 (Box 392, Folder 32)
      - Coquiot, Mauricia-Gustave, 1928 (Box 392, Folder 33)
      - Cornille & Cie., 1926-1928 (Box 392, Folder 34)
      - Cournault, Etienne, 1929-1930, undated (Box 392, Folder 35)
      - Courtin, Georges, 1927 (Box 392, Folder 36)
      - Cros, Jean, 1926 (Box 392, Folder 37)
      - Miscellaneous C, 1926-1930 (Box 392, Folder 38)
      - Danthon, G. (see Galerie Haussman) (Box 393)
      - Decoeur, Emile, 1926 (Box 393, Folder 1)
      - Decorchmont, F., 1926 (Box 393, Folder 2)
      - de Félice, Mlle., 1927-1930 (Box 393, Folder 3)
      - de Frenne, Ernest, 1928 (Box 393, Folder 4)
      - de la Faille, J. B., 1927-1930 (Box 393, Folder 5)
      - de Miré, Georges, 1930, undated (Box 393, Folder 6)
      - Dilly, A. C., 1926-1928 (Box 393, Folder 7)
      - Documents, 1929-1930 (Box 393, Folder 8)
      - Donop de Mouchy, le Baron, 1928-1929 (Box 393, Folder 9)
      - Draeger Frères, 1926-1930 (Box 393, Folder 10)
      - Drian, H., 1926-1927 (Box 393, Folder 11)
      - Dufrenoy, 1927 (Box 393, Folder 12)
      - Dunand, Jean, 1926-1927 (Box 393, Folder 13)
      - Dunoyer de Segonzac, André, 1926-1930 (Box 393, Folder 14)
      - Duval, Mme. Raoul (née Renée Vautier), 1926-1929 (Box 393, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous D, 1926-1930, undated (Box 393, Folder 16)
      - Editions Albert Lévy, 1926-1928 (Box 393, Folder 17)
      - Editions Cahiers d'Art, 1928-1930 (Box 393, Folder 18)
      - Editions des Quatre Chemins, 1929-1930 (Box 393, Folder 19)
      - Effort Moderne, 1930 (Box 393, Folder 20)
      - Einstein, Carl, 1929-1930 (Box 393, Folder 21)
      - Exposition Permanente des Oeuvres de R. Lalique, 1926 (Box 393, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous E, 1928-1930 (Box 393, Folder 23)
      - Faille, J. B., de la (see de la Faille, J. B.) (Box 393)
      - Félice, Mlle., de (see de Félice, Mlle.) (Box 393)
      - Fénéon, Felix, 1927-1930 (Box 393, Folder 24)
      - Flechtheim, Alfred, 1927-1930 (Box 393, Folder 25)
      - Frenne, Ernest de (see de Frenne, Ernest) (Box 393)
      - Fried, A., 1929, undated (Box 393, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous F, 1926-1930 (Box 393, Folder 27)
      - Galerie A. G. Fabre, 1928-1929 (Box 393, Folder 28)
      - Galerie Barbazanges, 1927-1929 (Box 393, Folder 29)
      - Galerie Bernier, 1928-1930 (Box 393, Folder 30)
      - Galerie Caspari, 1929-1930 (Box 393, Folder 31)
      - Galerie Colette Weil, 1927-1928 (Box 393, Folder 32)
      - Galerie d'Art Contemporain, 1927-1929 (Box 393, Folder 33)
      - Galerie d'Art du Montparnasse, 1928-1929 (Box 393, Folder 34)
      - Galerie Dru, 1927-1930, undated (Box 393, Folder 35)
      - Galeries Druet, 1927-1930 (Box 393, Folder 36)
      - Galerie Edgar Brandt (see Maison Brandt) (Box 393)
      - Galerie Haussmann, 1926-1930 (Box 394, Folder 1)
      - Galerie Hebrard, 1926-1929 (Box 394, Folder 2)
      - Galerie Granoff, 1927-1929 (Box 394, Folder 3)
      - Galerie Marcel Bernheim, 1926-1930 (Box 394, Folder 4)
      - Galerie Matthiesen, 1927-1929 (Box 394, Folder 5)
      - Galerie Percier, 1926-1930 (Box 394, Folder 6)
      - Galerie Pierre, 1927-1930 (Box 394, Folder 7)
      - Galerie Sèvres, 1930 (Box 394, Folder 8)
      - Galerie Simon, 1928-1930 (Box 394, Folder 9)
      - Galerie Van Leer, 1927, 1929 (Box 394, Folder 10)
      - Galerie Vignon, 1930 (Box 394, Folder 11)
      - Galerie Vildrac, 1928 (Box 394, Folder 12)
      - Galerie Zak, 1927-1929, undated (Box 394, Folder 13)
      - Galerien Thannhauser, 1927-1930 (Box 394, Folder 14)
      - Gauthier, R., 1928-1930 (Box 394, Folder 15)
      - Giafferri, Paul Louis de, 1928-1929 (Box 394, Folder 16)
      - Girard, Charles, 1926-1929 (Box 394, Folder 17)
      - Gold, Alfred, 1928-1930 (Box 394, Folder 18)
      - Gordon, Jan, 1929 (Box 394, Folder 19)
      - Grassoreille, Mlle. H., 1929-1930 (Box 394, Folder 20)
      - Gronkawski, Camille, 1926-1930 (Box 394, Folder 21)
      - Grosvallet, Edouard, 1928-1930 (Box 394, Folder 22)
      - Groult, Nicole, 1926, undated (Box 394, Folder 23)
      - Guérin, M. and Mme. Eugène, 1929-1930 (Box 394, Folder 24)
      - Guillaume, Paul, 1928-1930 (Box 394, Folder 25)
      - Guiot, Marcel, 1925-1928, undated (Box 394, Folder 26)
      - Gumsaragan, T., 1927-1928 (Box 394, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous G, 1926-1940, undated (Box 394, Folder 28)
      - Halicka, Alice, 1929, undated (Box 394, Folder 29)
      - Hayden, Henri, 1927-1928 (Box 394, Folder 30)
      - Heniot, Enrique L., 1929-1930 (Box 395, Folder 1)
      - Hessel, Joseph, 1926-1930 (Box 395, Folder 2)
      - Hodebert (see Galerie Barbazanges) (Box 395)
      - Horizons de France, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 3)
      - Houbre, Robert, 1929 (Box 395, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous H, 1927-1930 (Box 395, Folder 5)
      - Imprimerie Crété (see Revue de la Femme) (Box 395)
      - Independent Gallery (see Turner, Percy M.) (Box 395)
      - Iser, 1927 (Box 395, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous I, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 7)
      - Jester, Ralph, 1927 (Box 395, Folder 8)
      - Joyant, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 9)
      - Jumel, Lily, 1926-1930 (Box 395, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous J, 1926-1930 (Box 395, Folder 11)
      - Kann, Alphonse, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 12)
      - Kapferer, Marcel, 1928-1930 (Box 395, Folder 13)
      - Kelekian, Dikran Khan, 1929-1930 (Box 395, Folder 14)
      - Keller, René (see Galerie Barbazanges) (Box 395)
      - Klinkhardt & Biermann, 1929 (Box 395, Folder 15)
      - Klostermann, Paul, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous K, 1926-1930 (Box 395, Folder 17)
      - Lacroix, Boris Jean, 1929 (Box 395, Folder 18)
      - Lair Dubreuil, F., 1928-1930 (Box 395, Folder 19)
      - Lalique (see Exposition Permanente des Oeuvres de R. Lalique) (Box 395)
      - Lauzerte, Raymond, 1926-1929 (Box 395, Folder 20)
      - Lebel, Robert, 1929 (Box 395, Folder 21)
      - Ledoux, Picard, 1926 (Box 395, Folder 22)
      - Le Garrec, Maurice, 1925-1928 (Box 395, Folder 23)
      - Léger, Fernand, 1930 (Box 395, Folder 24)
      - Legrain, Pierre, 1926-1927 (Box 395, Folder 25)